

# About Me

I have over 5 years of relevant development experience.

Extensive experience developing using React.js/Next.js components along with Typescript, Redux, Redux Toolkit Query (RTK), React Query, SWR, Styledcomponents, React Hook Form and good use react UI components library and components. I can develop individual or with team Expertly applied API in coding Expert communication, development. interpersonal, and organizational skills. . And then I also have experience in remote job.



0960343113 ,0980329930 iessica17796



jessica.sy.dev@gmail.com



Casa Condo, Sukhumvit 97 Alley, Bang Chak, Phra Khanong, Bangkok 10260.



https://github.com/shweyeehtu nwatiaung

# **SKILLS SUMMARY**

- · React.js , Next.js , React Native
- Javascript, TypeScript
- MongoDb, Firebase
- JSON, HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, Radix UI, MUI, Tailwind.
- Familar with Flutter, Express Js, **Node**js
- Version Control System: GitHub, Bitbucket
- Design tools: Figma, Adobe XD

# (Jessica)

### **EXPERIENCE**

Frontend Developer

# Frontend Developer

May 2021 - Jun 2023

Za Information Technology Co., Ltd

Experienced in handling multi projects Successfully deliver the project before the project deadline.

Delivered quality projects such as:

- Hoco (Web, Mobile)
- Global Marketplace (Web)
- Zawgyi Mart (Web)
- Sweety Home (Mobile)

Tech: React js, Next js, Typescript, Flutter

#### Web Developer

Sept 2019 - Apr 2021

MMRD Co., Ltd

Worked to solve complex problems using the latest in Web Technologies. Planned, developed, tested, deployed, and maintained web applications.

• Yangon Directory, Mandalay Directory, Myanmar Restaurant Guide, My

**Tech**: React, Typescript, MUI, Tailwind.

#### Junior Frontend Developer

2017 - 2019

ITSquareCo., Ltd

# **EDUCATION**

National Management Degree

2015 - 2016

**College** 

Diploma in Information Technology

Technology University (Thanlyin)

2013 - 2017

Bachelor of Technology (B.Tech)

Technology University (Thanlyin)

2017 - 2019

Bachelor of Engineering (B.E)

### LANGUAGE

English